wingsfinancial.com 2006-06-20

# Privacy Policy

To assure the continued privacy and confidentiality of your personal financial information, Wings Financial observes these practices and procedures:

**Information We Collect**

We collect nonpublic personal information about you from some or all of the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms (such as your name, address, social security number, assets and income)
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others (such as your account balance, payment history, parties to transactions and credit card usage)
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency (such as your creditworthiness and credit history)

**Information We Disclose**

We do not disclose or sell information to non-affiliated businesses or third parties desiring access to our member information. We may disclose all of the information that we collect as described above to Wings Financial’s wholly or majority owned credit union service organizations or to those companies that perform marketing services on our behalf and agree to maintain the confidentiality of your nonpublic personal information.

We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you to non-affiliated third parties as permitted or required by law.

**Our Security Measures**

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products and service to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard our nonpublic personal information.

* * *

**Federal Regulation D (Reg. D)**

Reg. D requires the Credit Union to limit the number of automatic transfers from all accounts, excluding checking, but including World Class Money Market Accounts. These accounts are limited to a total of six (6) automatic transfers each period and no more than three of the six such transfers may be made by check, draft, debit card, or similar order made by the depositor and payable to third parties. The period is defined by the statement cycle of your accounts. If your statement cycle ends on the 7th of each month, that is your Reg D counter period. If you receive quarterly statements, your Reg D period is per calendar month. Transactions that are governed by Reg. D include transfers completed by telephone, CU PAL, CU Online, ACH, preauthorized transfers (excluding transfers to Credit Union loans), electronic payments/transfers and automatic transfers to a checking account to cover overdrafts.

Under Reg. D there is unlimited use of accounts for transactions completed by mail, ATM, or in person.

* * *

**External Link Disclaimer**

For our members' convenience, links are available in this Web site to allow quick access to other sites that may be of interest. Clicking on a link will take you out of Wings Financial’s Web site to an alternative site not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for the content of third party Web sites and does not represent either the third party Web site or the member if you enter into a transaction. Privacy and security policies of the above Web sites may differ from those practiced by Wings Financial.
